Finding Aid for the A&M Records Records PASC-M.0269
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sound recordings, 1910-1999; Series 12.
  - Non-commercial recordings, Subseries 1.; 175 items
    - Ghost Riders, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 20)
      On label, "BMB."
    - Gil's show, 1 sound cassette (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Greased Lightnin' Man, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Happy Mexican, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Hatari Theme, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: Cr-62614
    - Hello Happiness, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 14)
      From the Cinerama film, "Say Hello to Yesturday"
    - Herb Sterling, 1 sound cassette (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Herb Alpert, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 69, Folder 25)
      Contains a letter to Herb Alpert asking for verification of enclosed song.
    - Herb Alpert's Tijuana Brass, 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 29)
      Our Day Will Come -- Mexican Road Race -- I Will Wait For You -- Bean Bag -- The Wall Street Rag -- Flamingo Side -- The work Song -- Mame -- Blue Sunday -- Don't Go Breaking My Heart -- For Carlos -- Freight Train Joe.
    - High and Heavy, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Ho, Ho, Ho It's Me Again, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Honey's Day, No Way, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - How Little We Know, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 7)
      Also written by Hoagy Carmichael. Recorded by: Commercial Sound Recorders.
    - How Little We Know, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: CR 6-2614
    - I Didn't Do It, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - I Get Aong Wthout You Very Well, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - I Honestly Love You, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - I Walk With Music, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - I wouldn't Change the Man He Is, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Igor Nazaruk, 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 13)
      Tape #6
    - I'm Waitin' (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Improvisational Piano Piece, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Island, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - It's Good To Be Free, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - I've Still Got My Heart, Joe, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 4)
      Recorded at: Associated Recoring Studios.
    - Ivy, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Julius, 1972 April (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Jungle, 1986-1988; 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 22)
      Retired Circle -- April -- On a Shore -- Nostalgia -- Jazz -- [A few unprepared cuts from '89].
      On item, "tape #8 ."
    - Lady Love's Thunder, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Letta, 1976 July 22 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Life, 1 sound cassette (Box 64, Folder 17)
      Thunder -- Prelude -- Life Ain't Easy -- Isn't it Possible -- Show Me the Way -- Good Reason -- Devil Made Me Do It -- Socialitic Point of View.
    - Lighthouse, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Listen, 1988 September 9; 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 5)
      0-15:30 Voiceover
    - The Little Tune, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 25)
      On label, "Carol Kaye."
    - The Long Way Home, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 12)
      Recorded by: Electro-Vox.
    - Louis Jordan, 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Love Has Got Me, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Love Me, Try Me, 1971 September 16; music reel box (Box 68, Folder 11)
      box only
    - Love Me Try Me, 1971 September 16; 1 open reel audio tape (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Marcio Montarryoyos: Live Tracks, 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 9)
      What A Wonderful World -- Ritual -- Pantanal 1.
    - The Matador March, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Maybe Baby, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Maybe Baby, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - More Than That, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - The Morning of Love, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Moscow Saxophone Quintet, 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 1)
      tape #2
    - My Resistance Is Low, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - The New Moscow Jazz band, Jazz ensemble "Decima", 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Now That There's You, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 6)
      Female version.
    - Number One, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Barry Nystrom, music reel (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - One Night Stand, 1 open reel tape (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Org.-tunes, 1 sound cassette (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Orpheus, 1970 May 4; 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 12)
      Side 2.
    - Peace, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - A Perfect Paris Night, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 8)
      Also composed by Hoagy Carmichael. Recorded by: Commercial Sound Recorders.
    - Piano Concerto, 1 sound cassette (Box 64, Folder 3)
      90 minutes
    - Pieces of Mind, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Raggedy Ann, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 4)
      Also performed by: Dallas Frazier.
    - Rain and Tears (instrumental), 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 13)
      Recorded by: M. R. C. Music, Inc.
    - Randy, Colman Hawin, 1 sound cassette (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Red, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Reza, 1970 April 29; 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 12)
      Side 1.
    - The Right Night and Barry White, 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Roll It, 1974 January 16; 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Room no. 118, 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 18)
      On item, "No. 3."
    - Ryabov, Kondekov, etc., 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 3)
      Just One Of Those Things; Day Dream / Cole Porter -- I Mean You / Theloneous Monk -- Tune-Up / Miles Davis -- O Grand Amor / Jobim -- Mirage / Art Farmer.
    - Sabora Mi, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Save the Sunlight, 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 6)
      Classics IV
    - Sharon Ann & Warren G. Kuhl, Jr, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - She, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Simone, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 16)
      On label, "Test Pressing .. Henry Gross."
    - Skylark, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Song for you/ don't, 1 sound cassette (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - The Sporn, 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Steve Bassett, 1976 August 19; 1 sound cassette (Box 64, Folder 10)
      No Good For Her -- Trick Bag -- Not Lookin' For Another.
    - Still Life (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Strong Strong Wind, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Sunsets, Blackbirds, Sweethearts & Flowers, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Sunshine, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Sunshine In My Soul, 1972 February 8; music reel (Box 69, Folder 2)
      With: Letter to Herb Alpert.
    - Superscope Special Cases, 1 sound cassette (Box 64, Folder 9)
      On item, "#1."
    - Tear it on Down, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Thinking of You, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - This Time Last Summer (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - To Wait For Love, August 2, 1968; 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Tommy's Tune, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - TV Music Co., 1 sound cassette (Box 64, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: ci 6-3126
      Misty Streets and Falling Rain -- Tinkling Piano in the Night -- First Came the Dream -- Love That Stays in Dreams.
    - TV Music Co., 1 sound cassette (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Twenty Below, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Un Bromme Libre, 1 open reel audio tape (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - The Wailing of the Willow, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Walking to Jaurez, 1 8" sound disc (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - We Were Happy Then, 1 sound cassette (Box 63, Folder 2)
      Also performed by: Mike Barone.
    - Whatsinya, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 11)
      Recorded by: MCA Music.
    - When Two People Are In Love, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Where Forever Begins, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 9)
      Recorded by: Emidisc.
    - Who Knows Where the Time Goes, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Wild Fox, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Woman Talk, 1 sound cassette (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - You Choose a Fine Time, 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - You Were There All the Time, 1 10" sound disc (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Commercial 78 rpm sound recordings, Subseries 2.
    - Slim Gaillard Quartette (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: A-215
    - Ethel Water (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: B-10415
    - Freddy Martin and his Orchestra (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: B-11211
    - Spike Jones and his City Slickers (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: 30-0812
    - Horace Heidt and his Brigadiers (Box 49, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: 8229
    - Brunswick Military Band (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: 8466
    - Martha Raye (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: 8433
    - Carlos Molina's Tango Orchestra (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: 80010
    - Freddie Slack and his Orchestra (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: 102
      broken
    - Freddie Slack and his Orchestra (Box 49, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: 113
    - Johnny Mercer with Freddie Slack and his Orchestra (Box 49, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: 122
    - Ray McKinley and his Orchestra (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: 131
    - Jo Stafford with Paul Weston and his Orchestra (Box 49, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: 142
    - Ella Mae Morse with Dick Walters and his Orchestra (Box 49, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: 143
    - Ella Mae Morse with Dick Walters and his Orchestra (Box 49, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: 151
    - Ella Mae Morse (Box 49, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: 163
    - Stan Kenton (Box 49, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: 187
    - Jo Stafford with Paul Weston and his Orchestra (Box 49, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: 191
    - The King Cole Trio (Box 49, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: 208
    - John Mercer with Paul Weston (Box 49, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: 217
    - The King Cole Trio (Box 49, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: 224
    - Johnny Mercer with Pied Pippers (Box 49, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: 230
    - Nellie Lutcher and her Rhythm (Box 49, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: 40002
    - Leo F. Reisman Orchestra (Box 49, Folder 23)
      Publisher no.: A3366
    - Edwin Dale and William Morgan (Box 49, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: A3501
    - Andre Kostalanetz (Box 49, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: 4236
    - Nelson Eddy (Box 49, Folder 26)
      Publisher no.: 4241
    - Ethel Merman (Box 49, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: 23585
    - Ethel Merman and Ray Middleton (Box 49, Folder 28)
      Publisher no.: 23586
    - Ray Middleton (Box 49, Folder 29)
      Publisher no.: 23588
    - Annie Get Your Gun Chorus (Box 49, Folder 30)
      Publisher no.: 23589
    - Kay Kyser (Box 49, Folder 31)
      Publisher no.: 35295
    - Orin Tucker (Box 49, Folder 32)
      Publisher no.: 35328
    - Raymond Scott Quintet (Box 49, Folder 33)
      Publisher no.: 35347
    - Raymond Scott (Box 49, Folder 34)
      Publisher no.: 35363
    - Kay Kysler (Box 49, Folder 35)
      Publisher no.: 35368
    - Kay Kysler (Box 49, Folder 36)
      Publisher no.: 35411
    - Orin Tucker (Box 49, Folder 37)
      Publisher no.: 35468
    - Kay Kysler (Box 49, Folder 38)
      Publisher no.: 35473
    - Gene Krupa (Box 49, Folder 39)
      Publisher no.: 35508
    - Kay Kysler (Box 49, Folder 40)
      Publisher no.: 35518
    - Kay Kysler (Box 49, Folder 41)
      Publisher no.: 35554
    - Duke Ellington (Box 49, Folder 42)
      Publisher no.: 35556
    - Kay Kysler (Box 49, Folder 43)
      Publisher no.: 35563
    - Frankie Carle (Box 49, Folder 44)
      Publisher no.: 35570
    - Frankie Carle (Box 49, Folder 45)
      Publisher no.: 35572
    - Frankie Carle (Box 49, Folder 46)
      Publisher no.: 35573
    - Will Bradley (Box 49, Folder 47)
      Publisher no.: 35707
    - Spade Cooley (Box 50, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: 38054
    - Kay Kyser (Box 50, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: 35762
    - The Merry Macs (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: 2333
    - Kate Smith (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: 35778
    - Gypsy Ensemble (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: 36242
    - Danny Kaye (Box 50, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: 36582
    - Danny Kaye (Box 50, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: 36583
    - The Fairy Pipers (Box 50, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: 36584
    - Dinah -- eileen (Box 50, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: 36585
    - Chiu-chiu -- Brazil (Box 50, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: 36651
    - Soft hearted -- a touch of Texas (Box 50, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: 36671
    - The fuddy duddy watchmaker -- lets get lost (Box 50, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: 36673
    - You're so good to me -- pushin' sand (Box 50, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: 36676
    - You'll never know -- close to you (Box 50, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: 36678
    - If you please -- sunday, monday or always (Box 50, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: 36679
    - A lovely way to spend an evening -- I couldn't sleep a wink last night (Box 50, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: 36687
    - Suddenly its spring -- irresistible you (Box 50, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: 36693
    - In a little hula heaven -- never in a million years (Box 50, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: 1210
    - The old oaken bucket -- smiles (Box 50, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: 1821
    - Small fry -- laugh and call it love (Box 50, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: 1935
    - Summer souvenirs -- is that the way to treat a sweetheart? (Box 50, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: 2053
    - Honky tonk train -- the big noise from winnetka (Box 50, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: 2208
    - If i didn't care -- knock kneed sal (Box 50, Folder 23)
      Publisher no.: 2286
    - Missouri waltz -- home on the range (Box 50, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: 2676
    - Bluebirds in the moonlight -- it's a hap-hap-happy day (Box 50, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: 2834
    - I'm fit to be tied -- chatterbox (Box 50, Folder 26)
      Publisher no.: 2910
    - Run little rain drop run -- confucius say (Box 50, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: 2917
    - Memories of you -- i'm through (Box 50, Folder 28)
      Publisher no.: 2966
    - I,yi,yi,yi,yi -- in apple blossom time (Box 50, Folder 29)
      Publisher no.: 3622
    - No love, no nothin' -- you better give me lots of lovin', honey (Box 50, Folder 30)
      Publisher no.: 4427
    - On the sunny side of the rockies -- sweethearts or strangers (Box 50, Folder 31)
      Publisher no.: 5902
    - It ain't necessarily so -- a woman is a sometime thing (Box 50, Folder 32)
      Publisher no.: 18281
    - Be not disencouraged -- i dood it (Box 50, Folder 34)
      Publisher no.: 18506
    - Hot chestnuts -- four or five times (Box 50, Folder 35)
      Publisher no.: 18526
    - Apollo jump -- are you ready (Box 50, Folder 36)
      Publisher no.: 18529
    - My ideal -- besame mucho (Box 50, Folder 37)
      Publisher no.: 18574
    - These foolish things -- they say it's wonderful (Box 50, Folder 38)
      Publisher no.: 18829
    - Mama eu quero -- bambu-bambu (Box 50, Folder 39)
      Publisher no.: 23132
    - Pistol packin' mama -- vict'ry polka, 23277 (Box 50, Folder 40)
    - All er nothin' -- the surry with the fring on top (Box 50, Folder 41)
      Publisher no.: 23284
    - Look for the silver lining -- long ago (and far away) (Box 50, Folder 42)
      Publisher no.: 23317
    - Begin the beguine -- hand to mouth boogie (Box 50, Folder 43)
      Publisher no.: 23319
    - Is you is or is you ain't -- (There'll be a) hot time in the town of Berlin (when the Yanks go marching in) (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: 23350
    - Don't fence me in -- The three caballeros (Box 51, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: 23364
    - Say Persianna say -- Swanee River moon (Box 51, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: 4846
    - Call me back, pal o'mine -- I wish there was a wireless to heaven (Box 51, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: 4944
    - Ave Maria / Schubert -- Cradle song (Wiegenlied) / Brahms (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: 712
    - Music by the angels -- My heart cries for you (Box 51, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: 5563
    - Boogie woogie prayer (Box 51, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: 4006
    - I can't love you any more -- Sierra Sue (Box 51, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: 5521
    - The man don't come to our house anymore -- Bartender polka (Box 51, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: 5717
    - Virginia, Georgia and Caroline -- I'll be around (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Gee, but I'd like to make you happy -- It's really for you, 1926 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: 1424
    - You don't like it--not much -- I love no one but you, 1926 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: 2532
    - Besame mucho - bolero -- Como tru-cu-tu - rhumba (Box 51, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: 1059
    - The drag -- Mary Ann (Box 51, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: 2837
    - Not for a day but forever -- Pagan love song (Box 51, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: 4046
    - Cansado (I'm tired) - Rhumba -- Os quindis de yaya - Samba (Box 51, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: 1061
    - Cae cae - samba -- Llumbele - guarracha (Box 51, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: 1062
    - Johnny's messin' 'round -- She had to go and lose it at the Astor (Box 51, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: 8083
    - She really meant to keep it -- You've got me in the palm of your hand (Box 51, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: 8117
    - Would'st could I but kiss thy hand, oh babe -- The man who comes around (Box 51, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: 8143
    - Poinciana (song of the tree) -- Dancing in the dark-fox trot (Box 51, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: 20-1554
    - All the things you are-fox trot (Box 51, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: 20-1561
    - It might as well be spring -- Give me the simple life (Box 51, Folder 23)
      Publisher no.: 20-1738
    - Just a little lovin' -- My daddy is only a picture (Box 51, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: 20-3013
    - A lane in Spain -- Sweet Swanee lady (Box 51, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: 355
    - Dipsy doodle-fox trot -- Who?-fox trot (Box 51, Folder 26)
      Publisher no.: 25693
    - Could be-fox trot -- Penny serenade-tango fox trot (Box 51, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: 26150
    - Do nothin' till you hear from me-fox trot -- Chlo-e-fox trot (Box 51, Folder 28)
      Publisher no.: 20-1547
    - The little man who wasn't there-fox trot -- Parade of the wooden soldiers-fox trot (Box 51, Folder 29)
      Publisher no.: 26308
    - Ruspana one-step -- Have a smile medley fox trot (Box 51, Folder 30)
      Publisher no.: 18563
    - Annie Laurie -- Ben Bolt (Box 51, Folder 31)
      Publisher no.: 16388
    - Rosetime and you-fox trot -- Oh! Harold!-collegiate walk or fox trot (Box 51, Folder 32)
      Publisher no.: 19090
    - Rosie--medley fox trot -- Honolulu eyes--medley waltz (Box 51, Folder 33)
      Publisher no.: 18721
    - Medley of old time songs-waltz -- Victor Herbert medley waltz (Box 51, Folder 34)
      Publisher no.: 19082
    - Sweet Hawaiian girl of mine -- Honolulu honey (Box 51, Folder 35)
      Publisher no.: 18796
    - My mammy--medley fox trot -- Humming--medley fox trot (Box 51, Folder 36)
      Publisher no.: 18737
    - Green eyes: rumba -- Perdon: rumba (Box 51, Folder 37)
      Publisher no.: 27443
    - Let's do it again -- Don't make me sorry (Box 51, Folder 38)
      Publisher no.: 20-3899
    - The lady in red: rumba -- Estrellita: rumba, Broken (Box 51, Folder 39)
      Publisher no.: 27442
    - La bomba: rumba -- My shawl: rumba (Box 51, Folder 40)
      Publisher no.: 27441
    - It was only a sun shower -- What do we do on a dew-dew-dewy day? (Box 51, Folder 41)
      Publisher no.: 435
    - Souvenier de Vienne: waltz -- Because: waltz (Box 51, Folder 42)
      Publisher no.: 26659
    - Adios, Mariquita Linda: fox trot -- Frenesi: fox trot (Box 51, Folder 43)
      Publisher no.: 26542
    - Xavier Cugat (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: 27444
      Broken
    - David Rose and his orchestra (Box 52, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: 27853
    - Tommy Dorsey, Frank Sinatra (Box 52, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: 27947
    - John McCormack (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: 64311
    - John McCormack (Box 52, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: 64622
    - Sammy Kaye (Box 52, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: 3681
    - Cab Calloway (Box 52, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: 4753
    - Henry Russell (Box 52, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: 5221
    - Jan Garber (Box 52, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: 5253
    - Dick Jurgens (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: 5405
    - Hoosiers Hot Shots (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: 05547
    - Souvenir album (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: A-348
      Miss Otis Regrets; Moonglow; Give Me a Heart to Sing to; I Ain't Gonna Sing No More; Dinah; You're going to Leave the Old Home, Jim; You're a Sweetheart; I'll Get Along Somehow; When Its Sleppy Time Down South; How Can I Face this Wearied World Alone
    - Easter parade -- abraham, 18425 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Naughty 90's (Box 52, Folder 15)
      I Don't Care -- Smarty -- My Mother was a Lady -- Waiting at the Church -- Strike up the Band -- Oceana Roll -- Don't Go in the Lion's Cage Tonight -- The Nightingale.
    - Music of Latin America (Box 52, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: MS 463 - Series E
      Loca; Sorella
    - Favoritos (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Just Friends; Let's Fall in Love; I'll See You In My Dreams; Imagination; Maria Elena; La Borrachita; Cielito Lindo; Adios Muchachos
    - Tschaikowsky's Nutcracker Suite In Dance Tempo (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Commercial 45 rpm sound recordings, Subseries 3.
    Recordings are arranged alphabetically by performer.
    - Takeda-No-Komoriuta, 1 7" sound disc (Box 55, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: ETP-10324, side 1
      Japanese pressing.
    - Tsubasa-O-Kudasai, 1 7" sound disc (Box 55, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: ETP-10324, side 2
      Japanese recording.
    - [Unidentified], 1 7" sound disc (Box 55, Folder 44)
      Publisher no.: LK-51-Z
    - [Unidentified], 1 7" sound disc (Box 56, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: DR 6105
    - [Unidentified] (Box 56, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: DRQ 6902
    - Canada: a centennial song, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - [Unidentified], 1 7" sound disc (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Jivin' Around (Box 56, Folder 36)
      Publisher no.: 936X
    - 3 O'Clock Jump [mixes], 1989; 1 12" sound disc (Box 40, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: SP-12316
      12" disc.
    - [Compilation of dance mixes], 1987; 3 12" sound discs (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: SP-17499
      Red, white, and blue vinyl, 12" discs.
    - Keep Your Eye On Me, 1987; 12" disc (Box 40, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: USAT 602
      Extended version, 2 copies.
    - Red Hot, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: AM-2593
    - Oriental Eyes, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: AM-2621
    - Sweet Georgia Brown (Box 54, Folder 28)
      Publisher no.: 45-700, side 1
    - Viper's Blues (Box 54, Folder 28)
      Publisher no.: 45-700, side 2
    - Interview, 1967; 1 7" sound disc (Box 55, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: 1167-USA
      On label: Famous American Stars series presents an interview special with Herb Alpert.
    - Third Man Theme, 1 7" sound disc (Box 55, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: FX-11,096
      Third Man Theme -- Lemon Tree -- Butterball -- Tangerine
    - Fallout Shelter (Box 54, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: 701, side 2
    - Tell It To The Birds (Box 54, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: 701, side 1
    - Tell It To The Birds (Box 54, Folder 47)
      Publisher no.: 45-16396, side 2